export const questions = [
  {
    question: 'what day is the first in week',
    answer: 'SUNDAY'
  },
  {
    question: 'what month is first in year',
    answer: 'JANUARY'
  },
  {
    question: 'what do people drink in the morning',
    answer: 'COFFEE'
  },
  {
    question: 'what bird is the most popular',
    answer: 'PIGEONTTTT'
  },
  {
    question: 'where do peaople keep food',
    answer: 'REFRIGERAT'
  },
  {
    question: 'who teaches children in the school',
    answer: 'TEACHER'
  },
  {
    question: 'where do children go every morning',
    answer: 'SCHOOL'
  },
  {
    question: 'what vegetable is green',
    answer: 'CUCUMBER'
  },
  {
    question: 'what fruit is yellow',
    answer: 'PINEAPPLEP'
  },
  {
    question: 'where do books lay',
    answer: 'BOOKCASEAA'
  }, 
]